<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Dani Agung &#8211; School of Industrial and System Engineering</title>
	<atom:link href="https://sie.telkomuniversity.ac.id/author/daniagung/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://sie.telkomuniversity.ac.id</link>
	<description>FRI Juara</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Wed, 25 Oct 2017 00:55:34 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=5.2.6</generator>

<image>
	<url>https://sie.telkomuniversity.ac.id/wp-content/uploads/2017/05/cropped-1-32x32.png</url>
	<title>Dani Agung &#8211; School of Industrial and System Engineering</title>
	<link>https://sie.telkomuniversity.ac.id</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Telkom University Enlivened Indonesia Creative Industry in Human Resources Sector</title>
		<link>https://sie.telkomuniversity.ac.id/telkom-university-enlivened-indonesia-creative-industry-in-human-resources-sector/</link>
				<comments>https://sie.telkomuniversity.ac.id/telkom-university-enlivened-indonesia-creative-industry-in-human-resources-sector/#respond</comments>
				<pubDate>Wed, 25 Oct 2017 00:55:34 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Dani Agung]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Berita Kampus]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://sie.telkomuniversity.ac.id/?p=7912</guid>
				<description><![CDATA[Bandung, Telkom University &#8211; The fluctuation of creative industries in Indonesia seems to grow gradually from year to year, the uptake of information technology in various regions of the archipelago helps everyone to be able to produce creative work both physically &#8230; ]]></description>
								<content:encoded><![CDATA[<article class="entry">
<div class="entry-content">
<p><strong>Bandung, Telkom University &#8211;</strong> The fluctuation of creative industries in Indonesia seems to grow gradually from year to year, the uptake of information technology in various regions of the archipelago helps everyone to be able to produce creative work both physically and digitally. There needs to be support from various parties so that the brainware industry is still alive and growing.</p>
<p>As a university that supports creative industry, Creative Industry, School of Telkom University (FIK) held an annual seminar of 4th Bandung Creative Movement 2017 (BCM) on Monday (9/10) at Crowne Plaza Hotel, Bandung. Carrying the theme of &#8220;Role of Art, Design, and Technology in The Society&#8221;, focusing on the latest research and trends, as well as the future prospects of the creative industry.</p>
<p>The 4th BCM 2017 main objective is to provide a platform for researchers, creative workers, academics, and industry professionals from other countries to present research and development activities in Design, Society, Technology, and Business.</p>
<p>The seminar is a great opportunity for invited guests to share new ideas, and establish business and research links for future collaboration. The seminar was attended by delegates from various countries in Southeast Asia.</p>
<p>Keynote Speakers at this international seminar are Elisabeth Lazzaro, Professor of Creative Economy at Universite Libre de Bruxelles, Belgium, at Southern Methodist University, Dallas, USA and Padua University, Italy.</p>
<p>According to the creative industry in Indonesia is already able to compete in the international arena. It needs support from stakeholders so that creative industry players can continue to produce creative products. HR is</p>
<p>Also present Coordinating Ministry for Economic Affairs, Dr. Ir. Rudi Salahudin. According to the creative industry will grow rapidly forward supported by technology acceleration.</p>
<p>&#8220;First I give appreciation to FIK Telkom University for its active contribution in the field of Creative Industry especially in the field of Education To be able to grow and develop, we must be open and observant to see opportunities.&#8221; The current and future brainware / creative industry is expected to grow very rapidly.<br />
Rector of Telkom University, Professor Mochamad Ashari, M.Eng., Ph.D., revealed that Telkom University is ready to fill the HR sector as a contribution in the Creative Industry.</p>
<p>&#8220;In FIK, we have 5 fields of study, there are Visual Communication Design, Interior Design, Product Design, Textile and Textile Craft, and Intermedia Art, and the five concentrations are tailored to the needs of today&#8217;s creative industry.&#8221;</p>
<p>The creative industry in Indonesia contributes 7% of national GDP and absorbs 16 million workers. This year the target is 1000 trillion of total GDP.<br />
&#8220;So this event is part of the program to develop creative industries in Indonesia.We want to color the creative industries in Indonesia in the HR sector.&#8221; Ashari is optimistic.</p>
<p>The seminar continued with International Conference, Panel Discussion, Parallel Class, and Paper Publication.</p>
</div>
</article>
<div class="row">
<div class="col-md-4"></div>
<div class="col-md-4">
<p>&nbsp;</p>
</div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
							<wfw:commentRss>https://sie.telkomuniversity.ac.id/telkom-university-enlivened-indonesia-creative-industry-in-human-resources-sector/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
		<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
							</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
